Queer|Art|Film Collection MSS.327
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series II: Video recordings
  - Subseries A: Video recordings
    - Viva Ruiz presents "Ms. 45," - Introduction and Q&A, May 6, 2013; ID: 327.0059 (Box 2, Media ID: 327.0059)
      Program Content: Performance artist Viva Ruiz presents Abel Ferrara's 1981 film "Ms. 45." She has long been taken with this gritty urban fairy tale: "As a native New Yorker, I swoon over the images of NYC at its 1981 most romantically trashy, authentic and unsterilized = R E A L."
- Series III: 2014 Accretion (Box 3)
  Scope and Contents
  Contains advertisement flyers and 5 miniDV cassettes
  Arrangement
  This series has not been arranged by an archivist.
  Born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be available to researchers.